Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ichhoa (LinkedIn) ichhoa.com/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Elixir

Flask

NestJS

Certifications

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

Ich Hoa Nguyen

DevOps Engineer

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Summary

Languages: Javascript/Typescript, Java, Python

Frameworks: NestJS, ExpressJS, FastifyJS, ElectronJS, ReactJS,

Django, Flask, Spring Boot

Databases: Mysql, Postgres, MongoDB, SQL Server, Redis

Tools: Git, Docker, K8S

Cloud: AWS, GCP

IaC: Terraform, Cloudformation

Total Exp: 3 Years

Experience

Saigon Technology - Global Software Development Company DevOps Engineer

September 2024 - Present (7 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

NAPA Global

2 years 2 months

DevOps Engineer

May 2023 - August 2024 (1 year 4 months)

Vietnam

Software Engineer

July 2022 - May 2023 (11 months)

Vietnam

Freelance

Software Engineer

July 2020 - November 2023 (3 years 5 months)

Vietnam

Developer Student Club - Danang University of Science and

Technology

1 year 10 months

Technical Leader July 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 1 month) Da Nang City, Vietnam

Back End Developer October 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 2 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

Education

Danang University of Science and Technology

Engineer's degree, Computer Science · (August 2019 - September 2023)